Jaehoon Jung

(631)838-1305 | hoon7589@gmail.com | https://jayjung98.github.io/ | https://www.linkedin.com/in/jayjungnote/

PROFILE

Data analyst who is helping in solving a problem such as business decisions through the analysis algorithm, and machine learning. A data analyst has the following skills. First is analytical thinking. I think it's important for a data analyst to know what to analyze and to provide a solution that fits. I can find and visualize effective data models on large datasets. Second, basic development knowledge. I gained basic development knowledge through programming experience that I learned in school and personal project experience.

EDUCATION

Stony Brook University, Stony Brook, NYJanuary 2019 – December 2022Bachelor of Science in Applied Mathematics and StatisticsMajor GPA: 3.31/4.00Angelo State University, San Angelo, TXAugust 2017 – December 2019Bachelor of Science in Computer ScienceGPA: 3.71/4.00

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python, R, SQL, Java, C++

Software and Integrated Development Environments (IDEs): Jupyter Notebook, GitHub, Microsoft

Visual Studio, Google Colab, RStudio, Eclipse, MS Acess

Languages: English – proficient, Korean - native

PROJECTS

Rossmann Store Sales, Kaggle Competition (https:///www.kagle.com/competitions/)

- Computed and visualized important features.
- Computed the best prediction of this data.

Roan and Repayment, Kaggle Competition (https:///www.kagle.com/competitions/)

- Computed which factors impact on whether the loan is repaid or not.
- Visualized the result and provided the interpretation of the resulting values.

Mobile Data Classification, Kaggle

- Computed cross-validation-score of each data model.
- Compared and evaluated the performance of each the following models: logistic regression, decision tree classifier, random forest classifier, Ada boosting, and Gradient boosting decision tree.

Soccer Player Analyzing

- Interpreted players to scout from European league players and remove from team squad.
- Computed and visualized specific personal skills using computer software.

EXPERIENCE

Army at Republic of Korea, Sergeant, Honorable discharged

Goseong, Kangwon-do

• Served in the general outpost at Go-Seong.

January 2020 – August 2021

• Executed a mission to monitor and analyze the enemies.

ACTIVITIES

English Peer Tutoring for International Students, Member of Bridge Tutor

San Angelo, TX

• Provided fun student-led, language-learning environment.

August 2017 – December 2019

Korea Student Association, Member of Welfare

San Angelo, TX

• Provided opportunities to learn Korean culture and language.

August 2017 – December 2019

• Hold K-Pop concert for San Angelo people.

Korean Life Media, Data Collector

Stony Brook, NY

• Executed collect and design data for the monthly radio broadcast. A

August 2019 – December 2019